Guide to the Time Inc. Advertising Promotion and Circulation Promotion Files 1922-2004 (bulk, 1923-1989) MS 3009-RG 21
New-York Historical Society
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: General, 1980 October-December (Offsite-box 3479, Folder 11-13)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "B-404. Fortune Magazine. :60 Cash Management Account."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 1. :60 Radio Oil Hunt F80-4-60."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "B-468. Fortune Magazine. 11/3-11/7 Airdate. 1. French Chefs :60 Radio."
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: General, 1980 October-December (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 1)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "B-554. Fortune Magazine. Week of December 2. 1. :60 Radio 'Suburbia' F-80-7-60."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "B-520 Remix. Fortune Magazine. Week of 11/17 Air Dates. 1. :60 Radio 'Corporate Crimes.'"
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1980: 50th Anniversary (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 8-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1981: General, 1981 January-February (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 2-4)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 'Corporate Loyalty.'"
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 'Proctor & Gamble.'"
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1981: General, 1981 March-April (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 5-6)
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 'The Reagan Plan.' :60."
  1 audiocassette: analog; 3 7/8 x 2 1/2 in., 1/8 in. tape. On label: "Fortune Magazine. 'Steel Industry.' Rev."
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1981: General, 1981 May-December (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 7-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1981: Fortune Subject Index (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: 1982-1989: General (Offsite-box 3480, Folder 11-16)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Christmas, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Fortune 500: "50 Years of the 500" Deck of Cards, 2004 February (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Fortune at Work, 1944-1963 (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 3-7)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Defense Information Program, 1965-1967 (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 8-9)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Cover Test, Cambridge Marketing Group, 1974 (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Readership, 1930-1945 (Offsite-box 3481, Folder 11-15)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Readership, 1953 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Readership, Automotive, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 2)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Readership, Miscellaneous, 1946-1951 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 3-4)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Market Research: Subscriber Check, 1930-1952 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 5-12)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Newsletters, 1930-1931 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 13)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Newsletters Index, 1938 (Offsite-box 3482, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Result Letters, 1940-1970 (Offsite-box 3483, Folder 1-10)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Testimonials: "Fortune Means Business", 1941-1947 (Offsite-box 3483, Folder 11)
- Fortune: Advertising Promotion: Testimonials: Miscellaneous, 1930-1933 (Offsite-box 3483, Folder 12)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: House Ads and Inserts, 1957-1976 (Offsite-box 3483, Folder 13-30)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Magazine Inserts, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 3483, Folder 31-34)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Magazine Inserts, 1962-1978 (Offsite-box 3484, Folder 1-17)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Space Ads and Inserts, 1958-1976 (Offsite-box 3484, Folder 18-34)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Ads and Inserts: Tip-ons, 1964 (Offsite-box 3484, Folder 35)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Early Subscriptions, 1929-1930 (Offsite-box 3484, Folder 36-38)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Acknowledgements, 1930-1951 (Offsite-box 3485, Folder 1)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Billings, 1930-1977 (Offsite-box 3485, Folder 2-22)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1929-1934 (Offsite-box 3485, Folder 23)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1935-1946 (Offsite-box 3486, Folder 1-18)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1947-1967 (Offsite-box 3487, Folder 1-21)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas, 1968-1976 (Offsite-box 3488, Folder 1-9)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas Billings, 1951-1957 (Offsite-box 3488, Folder 10)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas Card Samples, 1930-1956 (Offsite-box 3488, Folder 11-13)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Christmas Miscellaneous, 1946-1949 (Offsite-box 3488, Folder 14)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1930-1950 (Offsite-box 3488, Folder 15-22)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1951-1962 (Offsite-box 3489, Folder 1-19)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Direct Mail, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 3490, Folder 1-17)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1930-1937 (Offsite-box 3490, Folder 18-25)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1938-1944, 1955-1962 (Offsite-box 3491, Folder 1-21)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Mailings: Renewals, 1963-1977 (Offsite-box 3492, Folder 1-14)
- Fortune: Circulation Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1934-1968 (Offsite-box 3492, Folder 15)
- Fortune International: Advertising Promotion: Ads, 1965-1966 (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 10)
- Fortune International: Advertising Promotion: Booklets and Materials, 1952-1967 (Offsite-box 3492, Folder 16-17)
- Fortune International: Advertising Promotion: Booklets and Materials, 1963-1967 (Offsite-box 3464, Folder 11)
- Fortune International: Advertising Promotion: Miscellaneous, 1985 (Offsite-box 3492, Folder 18)
- HBO/Cinemax: Advertising Promotion, 1984 (Offsite-box 3492, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1936-1945: General (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 1-10)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1946: By Issue (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1946: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1947: By Issue (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1947: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1948: By Issue (Offsite-box 3493, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1948: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1949: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1949: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1950: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1950: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1951: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1951: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1952: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1952: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1953: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1953: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 12-13)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1954: By Issue (Offsite-box 3494, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1954: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1955: By Issue (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1955: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1956: By Issue (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1956: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 5-6)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1957: By Issue (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1957: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 8-9)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1958: By Issue (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1958: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 11-12)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1959: By Issue (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1959: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3495, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1960: By Issue (Offsite-box 3496, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1960: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3496, Folder 2-3)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1961-1966: General (Offsite-box 3496, Folder 4-15)
- Life: Advertisers Lists: 1967-1972: General (Offsite-box 3497, Folder 1-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1936: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1936: Mechanical Specifications for Ads, 1936 August? (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Circulation (Offsite-box 3497, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1937: "The Life Force in Retail Selling" (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3497, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1937: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Circulation (Offsite-box 3497, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: General Presentation (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: "The Life Force in Retail Selling" (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #1 (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Market Research: NAMP [Association of National Advertisers] Study (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1938: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Circulation (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: "Letters Advertisers Write to Life" (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #2 (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Rates (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1939: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Circulation (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: "How Life Sells for You" (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #3-4 (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 14-15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: "The Pace of Life" (Offsite-box 3530, Item 1-4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Rates (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: "Report on Life's Activities in Super Markets" (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1940: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3529, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Advertising Report (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Circulation (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: "Continuity and Concentration" (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #5 (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 22)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: "The Pace of Life" (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 2-3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Rates (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 23)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 24)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1941: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Circulation (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 25)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: "Let's Have the Facts" (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 26)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #6 (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 27)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3498, Folder 28)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Rates (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1942: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Circulation (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: "Circulation and Audience Today" (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Comments from Retailers (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Market Research: "Impact of War on American Families" (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #7 (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Rates (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1943: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: "Heavy Traffic on a Single Track" (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Rates (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1944: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Circulation (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: "Life Lines that Pull" (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Market Research: "Readability" (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Market Research: "What's Ahead for Advertising?" (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Rates (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1945: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3531, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Circulation (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946-1951: Libbey Glass (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 1-2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #8 (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 22-23)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Market Research: Roper, Automobile and Retailers (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 24)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 25)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Rates (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 26)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 27)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: "This Curious World" (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 28)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1946: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: "Life and the Merchants of Main Street" (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #9, 1946 (Offsite-box 3499, Folder 29)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Market Research: Continuing Study of Magazine Audiences (CSMA) #9 (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Rates (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1947: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Circulation (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: IGA Food Stores (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Market Research: "Chronolog" (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Market Research: Election Polls vs. Market Research (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Market Research: Hunt Foods (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Market Research: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Rates (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Sales Convention, 1948 May-September (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 13-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1948: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 10-11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 12-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: "It's the Last Yard that Counts" (Offsite-box 3532, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Market Research and TV: DuBois Study (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 16-17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Market Research and TV: Politz, Accumulative Audience (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 18-19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Merchandising Price Lists (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 21)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Rates (Offsite-box 3500, Folder 22)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1949: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 4-5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Market Research and TV: Politz, Accumulative Audience (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Rates (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 7)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1950: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 9-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Circulation (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Market Research and TV: Armed Forces Survey (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Market Research and TV: Politz (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Market Research and TV: Politz, Life Market (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: "Memorable Life Photographs" (Offsite-box 3533, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: "Mighty Mites" (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Proctor and Gamble (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Rates (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 17)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: "Spanish Village" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: TV Spots (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 18)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: "What Happens When Life Hits..." (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951-1952: "What's in a Picture?" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3501, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1951: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 7-10)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Conventions, Political (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 11)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Circulation (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 1)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: "Happy Christmas Little Friend" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 12)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: "Life Sells" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 13)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Market Research and TV: Politz, Accumulative Audience (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 2)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 3)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Rates (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 4)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Retail Representatives (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 5)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Sales Convention (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 6)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 7-8)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1952: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Ads: "How I Feel about Life" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 15)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Ads: "Impact" (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 16)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Ads: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 17-19)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Circulation (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 9)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: General Foods (Offsite-box 3534, Folder 20)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Market Research and TV: Politz, Four Media Study (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 10-14)
- Life: Advertising Promotion: 1953: Market Research and TV: Miscellaneous (Offsite-box 3502, Folder 15)